const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '187 + 113 =', answer: '300', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '241 + 159 =', answer: '400', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '243 + 157 =', answer: '400', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '312 + 188 =', answer: '500', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '431 + 169 =', answer: '600', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '463 + 237 =', answer: '700', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '524 + 276 =', answer: '800', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '543 + 357 =', answer: '900', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '311 + 189 =', answer: '500', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '134 + 266 =', answer: '400', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];